fustany.com 2019-05-24

# Arab Fashion Magazine for Middle East Women, Beauty Tips, Latest

**Privacy Policy**

**Effective Date: This Privacy Policy was last revised on May 22nd, 2018.**

You have arrived at a web site that is provided by Fustany Ltd. (“Fustany” or “we,” “our” or “us”). This “Privacy Policy” governs your use of www.fustany.com (including, without limitation, both mobile and online versions of our web sites, and also applies to your use of all features, applications, content, downloads and other services that we make available through these web sites and/or that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, referred to herein as the “Site”), regardless of how you access or use the Site, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise. This Privacy Policy does not apply to our data collection activities offline or otherwise outside of our Service (unless otherwise stated below).

**GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation):** With the update of this Privacy Policy, we hereby acknowledge that we are GDPR compliant, be it with:

a. The advertisers we work with.

b. The information the user provides us with, which they have the right to access at any given point, edit it or even delete it.

c. Any information provided by the user to Fustany, will only be used for the purpose the user provided it for, which falls under one of two categories. Category 1: Providing email, name and country to subscribe to a newsletter to receive Fustany’s latest content. Category 2: Creating an account on Fustany to access exclusive features, with personal information provided such as name, username, email and country being accessible at any time for the user, whether to view, edit or delete it.

**DATA:** We collect but do not link personal and activity data.

We collect but do not link personal and activity data.

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience.

We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address, which will not be used for any purposes other than the ones you had previously agreed on.

Our systems are not designed to associate personal information with your activities (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly remove the information.

**LOCATION:** We do not access your precise location.

We do not collect, use or share your precise geographic location.

**ACCESS:** You can request to see or delete your personal data.

You can sign into your account to see or delete any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, address, email or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see or delete this information.

**DELETION:** We keep personal data until you delete it.

We remove personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email or phone number) and other preferences associated with your account promptly after you delete your account. We may retain other data indefinitely.

**SHARING:** We don't share your personal information with marketers.

We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies for marketing purposes.

**AD TRACKING:** Ad companies collect anonymous data. You can opt out.

Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity.

**CONTACT:** You can ask privacy questions.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us:

info@fustany.com

11, 273 street, New Maadi, Cairo, Egypt.

**VENDORS:** Analytics providers access data on our behalf.

Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data.

**SECURITY:** We take steps to protect personal information.

We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.

**SPECIAL:** Special situations may require disclosure of your data.

To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so.

**MORE: You can review more privacy-related information.**

This privacy policy was last updated on May 22nd, 2018. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text.
